There are many mediclaim policies in the market,
but find out why this policy is special.
[Music]
Good morning friends,
welcome to SK Health & Wealth. Friends, you must have
seen that there are many products
for the common people, but there is a
product which is for the premium class people.
Tata AIG has recently launched a
mediclaim product which is called
Premium Product because it is
for the premier class people only.
Its premium price is very
reasonable, but its features are
amazing. Friends, when you make videos with great effort, you deserve
a like. When you like, you should
also share. And
when you progress so much, you should
definitely subscribe to the channel. Only then will you
get regular notifications, so you will be
able to enjoy those videos. If you have
permission, you will be able to take advantage of it. The most
exclusive feature is global coverage.
Friends, if the insured ever gets any such
disease or such treatment is
not available in India, then that person can go out of the
country across the globe for
treatment, like Singapore.
[Music]
This feature is very easily available without any extra premium
and if it is available somewhere then it is for an
extra premium. The second excuse
benefit is air ambulance. Friends, if you
see, this facility is not available in maximum cases,
but this
facility is also available in this policy. If for some
reason the patient has to be uplifted, that
too in an air ambulance, then that too up to ₹5 lakh
coverage is available in it.
Alternative treatment. Friends, it is not
necessary to always have allopathic treatment.
Nowadays, people
also go for AYUSH treatment for their life or body,
like Ayurvedic, Unani,
Homeopathy, you
can go to any such online medical facility because
nowadays many people are becoming more conscious about their health
and all these lines are
also becoming very active and people
get themselves treated very comfortably and very easily because there
is less pain in it and its treatment lasts a little longer,
but
good organ donor benefit. Friends,
if the patient ever gets into such a situation that he has to
harvest organs from other people.
Like the most common thing in the body is
kidney, liver, any such organ,
when it is transplanted then
whatever expenses are there in it like the cost of paint, all that
cost is borne by the company. Oct-
care procedure. Nowadays many such
treatments have started happening which do
not require 24 hour hospital.
Most commonly, like the operation of a slit in the eye,
which is completed in two-three-four hours,
for that you get full compensation.
Whatever expenses are incurred in bringing the patient from home to hospital or from hospital to home, the
company clears that. I will tell you one
trick also, like if there is an
accident on the road, then
whatever expenses are incurred in taking the patient from the road to the hospital, the
company
bears all that. Generally, you must have seen
friends, first the person gets the treatment done at home
and when the seriousness increases, only then the person gets treatment done,
but that money is
not your cashless money, you have to
spend it from your pocket, so
whatever expenses are incurred in time, 50 days are borne by the company.  The
entire expense of seeing the doctor,
any investigation, all the expenses of medicine are
covered for 60 days, then for however
many days you are in the hospital, be it
15 days or 20 days, all the expenses are covered after that,
you get a safe period, that is,
for the entire six months, a doctor will see you,
your medicines, any kind of
testing, because when a person recovers,
then the doctor also does testing once, whether
you are fully covered or
not, whether you have recovered or not, then charges are levied
for that too, so the expenses
are always applicable, here all the risk
is available and is given as courage, generally in
whichever policy you see, there is pre-
workplace and your home place is applicable for 60 days
only, but this policy
exclusively gives you the benefit of 60 days and 188 days,
sometimes you must have seen
friends
that the patient does not have space in his hospital, there is
no room, so
how will the person be admitted in it or can it be  It is
that the patient is not in such a condition that we
can remove him or shift him to the hospital, so
if the doctor insists
that the patient can be treated at home, then it is
called donation, the company bears the entire cost of this also,
if it is said that the patient can be treated
at home and hospital during the policy
period and there is a lot of other coverage that is available, there is
another exclusive benefit in it that is mental illness,
if
during the policy period if
a person gets mentally ill anywhere, then
that is also covered in this policy, which is
usually not covered in 99% of the policies
and one exclusive benefit is
consumable benefit, friends, you must have seen
many times that your expenditure is,
let's say, two and a half lakh, but the
company has given you 280 thousand rupees, 35000 rupees
because that banda which is 20 thousand rupees,
like hand gloves or many other
nebulizers, there are many such which are on the
shoulder  These come under the pay benefit category, which they
call out of pocket expenses and they have to
share their pockets, but here
you won't have to pay a single rupee from your pocket, the
entire money will be provided to you by the company,
here too your entire treatment will be cashless,
anywhere in India. Don't
think that you can get treatment only in that city, consider it to be
Kolkata,
and you have to get treatment, be it Delhi,
Mumbai, Madras, you can go anywhere,
and even go to small cities,
this is the news, friends, I have
told you the features, study the features of other companies as well,
if you are currently
searching for any other company,
then don't worry, you
can also switch to any policy, the benefits of your old
policy will be restored here
and you can easily avail its benefits,
stay happy and take such a policy that
you too are free, we hold special insurance
[Music]